Send My Love (To Your New Lover)
Just the guitar, okay cool
-==[ www.OpenSubtitles.com ]==-
This was all you, none of it me
You put your hands on, on my body and told me
Mmm
You told me you were ready
For the big one, for the big jump
I'd be your last love everlasting you and me
Mmm
That was what you told me
I'm giving you up
I've forgiven it all
You set me free-ee
Send my love to your new lover
Treat her better
We've gotta let go of all of our ghosts Treat her better
We've gotta let go of all of our ghosts
We both know we ain't kids no more We've gotta let go of all of our ghosts
We both know we ain't kids no more
Send my love to your new lover We both know we ain't kids no more
Send my love to your new lover
Treat her better Send my love to your new lover
Treat her better
We gotta let go of all of our ghosts
We both know we ain't kids no more
I was too strong you were trembling
You couldn't handle the hot heat rising I was too strong you were trembling
You couldn't handle the hot heat rising
Mmm
Baby I'm still rising
I was running, you were walking
You couldn't keep up, you were falling down (down)
Mmm
Mmm there's only one way down
I'm giving you up
I've forgiven it all
You set me free-ee, oh
Send my love to your new lover
Treat her better
We gotta let go of all of our ghosts
We both know we ain't kids no more
Send my love to your new lover
Treat her better
We've gotta let go of all of our ghosts
We both know we ain't kids no more
If you're ready, if you're ready
If you're ready, I am ready
We both know we ain't kids no more