[Song: Hey Brother by Avicii]
Hey brother
there's an endless road to re-discover
Hey sister
know the water's sweet but blood is thicker
Oh, if the sky comes falling down,
for you
There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do
Hey brother
do you still believe in one another?
Hey sister
do you still believe in love I wonder
if the sky comes falling down
for you
There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do
What if I'm far from home
Oh brother, I will hear you call
What if I lose it all
Oh sister, I will help you out
Oh, if the sky comes
falling down,
for you
There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do
Hey brother,
there's an endless road to re-discover
Hey sister,
do you still believe in love, I wonder
Oh, if the sky comes falling down
for you
There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do
What if I'm far from home?
Oh brother, I will hear you call
What if I lose it all
Oh sister, I will help you out
Oh, if the sky comes falling down,
for you
There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do
Tell me another story.
I think it's time for you to tell me a story
Why do you have to go, Dad
I promise I'll be back in no time.
The End