Ooh, yeah
I'll admit, I was wrong
What else can I say, girl?
Can't you break my head and not my heart?
I was drunk, I was gone, that don't make it right
But I promise there were no feelings involved
She said "Boy, tell me honestly
Was it real or just for show?" Yeah
She said "Save your apologies
Baby, I just gotta know"
How long has this been going on?
You've been creeping 'round on me
While you're calling me baby
How long has this been going on?
You've been acting so shady
I've been feeling it lately, baby
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I'll admit, it's my fault
But you gotta believe me
When I say it only happened once
I tried and I tried, but you'll never see that
You're the only one I wanna love, ooh, yeah
She said "Boy, tell me honestly
Was it real or just for show?"
She said "Save your apologies
Baby, I just gotta know"
How long has this been going on?
You've been creeping 'round on me
While you're calling me baby
How long has this been going on?
You've been acting so shady
I've been feeling it lately, baby
How long has this been going on, baby?
You gotta go tell me now
She said "Boy, tell me honestly
Was it real or just for show?" Yeah
She said "Save your apologies
Baby, I just gotta know"
How long has this been going on?
You've been creeping 'round on me
While you're calling me baby
How long has this been going on?
You've been acting so shady
I've been feeling it lately, baby
How long has this been going on?
You've been creeping 'round on me
How long has it been going on, baby?
How long has this been going on?
(You gotta go tell me now)
You been acting so shady
I've been feeling it lately, baby
dOn
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today