Whoa oh oh hm
You've been runnin' round, runnin' round, runnin' round throwin' that dirt all on my name
'Cause you knew that I, knew that I, knew that I'd call you up
You've been going round, going round, going round every party in LA
'Cause you knew that I, knew that I, knew that I'd be at one
I know that dress is karma, perfume regret
You got me thinking 'bout when you were mine
And now I'm all up on ya, what you expect
But you're not coming home with me tonight
You just want attention
You don't want my heart
Maybe you just hate the thought of me with someone new
Yeah, you just want attention
I knew from the start
You're just making sure I'm never gettin' over you
You've been runnin' round, runnin' round, runnin' round throwing that dirt all on my name
'Cause you knew that I, knew that I, knew that I'd call you up
Baby, now that we're, now that we're, now that we're right here standing face to face
You already know, already know, already know that you won
Ohh
I know that dress is karma, perfume regret
You got me thinking 'bout when you were mine
And now I'm all up on ya, what you expect
Oh baby
But you're not coming home with me tonight
You just want attention
You don't want my heart
Maybe you just hate the thought of me with someone new
Yeah, you just want attention
I knew from the start
You're just making sure I'm never gettin' over you (oh you)
Ohh
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', love?
(What are you doin'?)
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', love?
(What are you doin'?)
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', love?
(What are you doin'?)
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', love?
I know that dress is karma,
perfume regret
You got me thinking 'bout
when you were mine
And now I'm all up on
ya, what you expect
But you're not coming
home with me tonight
You just want attention
You don't want my heart
Maybe you just hate the thought
of me with someone new
Yeah, you just want attention
I knew from the start
You're just making sure I'm
never gettin' over you
(Over you)
What are you doin' to me? (heyy)
What are you doin', love? (What
are you doin', what?)
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', love? (Yeah,
you just want attention)
What are you doin' to me?
(I knew from the start)
What are you doin' love?
(You're just making sure I'm
never gettin' over you)
What are you doin' to me?
What are you doin', huh?
By ImperialPilotCore™