RaMANs
We don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
We don't love anymore
What was all of it for
Oh, we don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
I just heard you found
You've been looking for
I wish I would have known
that wasn't me
Cause even after all this time
I still wonder
Why I can't move on
Just the way you did so easily
Don't wanna know
What kind of dress
You're wearing tonight
If he's holding onto you so tight
The way I did before
I overdosed
Should've known your love was a game
Now I can't get you out of my brain
Oh, it's such a shame
That we don't talk anymore
We don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
We don't love anymore
What was all of it for
Oh, we don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
I just hope
You're lying next to somebody
Who knows how to love you like me
There must be a good reason
That you're gone
Every now and then I think
You might want me
To come show up at your door
But I'm just too afraid
That I'll be wrong
Don't wanna know
If you're looking into her eyes
If she's holding onto you so tight
The way I did before
I overdosed
Should've known your love was a game
Now I can't get you out of my brain
Oh, it's such a shame
That we don't talk anymore
We don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
We don't love anymore
What was all of it for
Oh, we don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
Support us and become VIP member to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Don't wanna know
What kind of dress
You're wearing tonigh
If he's giving it to you just right
The way I did before
I overdosed
Should've known your love was a game
Now I can't get you out of my brain
Oh, it's such a shame
That we don't talk anymore
We don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
We don't love anymore
What was all of it for
Oh, we don't talk anymore
Like we used to do
We don't talk anymore
That we don't talk anymore