Be My Woman Girl, And I'll Be Your Man
Be My Woman Girl, And I'll Be Your Man (Now)
Yes I'll Be Your Woman, Yes I'll Be Your Baby
Yes I'll Be Whatever That You Tell Me When You're Ready
Yes I'll Be Your Girl, Forever Your Lady
You Ain't Ever Gotta Worry, I'm Down For You Baby
Best Believe That, When You Need That
I'll Provide That, You Will Always Have It
I'll Be On Deck, Keep It In Check
When You Need That, I'ma Let You Have It
Beating My Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Like The Dirty Rhythm You Play
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Banging The Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Know You Want It In The Worst Way
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Be My Woman Girl, And I'll Be Your Man
Yes I Do The Cooking, Yes I Do The Cleaning
Plus I Keep The Na-Na Real Sweet For Your Eating
Yes You Be The Boss And Yes I Be Respecting
Whatever That You Tell Me Cause It's Game You Be Spitting
Oh Best Believe That, When You Need That
I'll Provide That, You Will Always Have It
I'll Be On Deck, Keep It In Check
When You Need That, I'ma Let You Have It
Beating My Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Like The Dirty Rhythm You Play
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Banging The Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Know You Want It In The Worst Way
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Be My Woman Girl, And I'll Be Your Man
Whole Crew Got The Juice, Your Dick Came The Truth
My Screams Is The Proof, Them Other Dudes Get The Deuce
When I Speed In The Coupe, Leavin' This Interview
It Ain't Nothing New, I Been Fucking With You
None Of Them Bitches Ain't Taking You, Just Tell 'Em To Make A U
That's How It Be, I Come First Like Debut
So Baby When You Need That
Gimme The Word, I'm No Good, I'll Be Bad For My Baby
Make Sure That He's Getting His Share
Make Sure That His Baby Take Care
Make Sure I'm On My Toes, On My Knees
Keep Him Pleased, Rub Him Down, Be A Lady And A Freak
Beating My Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Like The Dirty Rhythm You Play
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Banging The Drum Like Dum Di-Di-Day
I Know You Want It In The Worst Way
I Wanna Hear You Callin' My Name
Like, Hey Ma-Ma-Mama, Hey Ma-Mama
Be My Woman Girl, And I'll Be Your Man
alidnobilem.co.id