you got that
you got that milk money
i got that
i got that milf money
you got that
you got that milk money
i got that
i got that milf money
heard you're in the mood
for a little milfshake
welcome to the dairy
dutchess love factory
i could whip it up fix
you up straight away
c'mon in the front door
leavin' out
the back door
whip it flip it hay
been workin'
at your service
to give it to ya
didn't mean to
make you nervous
you mutha fucka
you got that
you got that milk money
i got that
i got that milf money
me and the girls
up in the club
hatin' ass ho's but
i don't give a fuck
runnin' a muck
ownin' the spot
buyin' the bar like i
bought all these rocks
i've been
workin' all week
now where the
hell is my drink
hair and
nails on fleek
all my girls on fleek
cuz we
i-n-d-e-p-e-n-d-e-n-t
do you know
what that means
can't see me b-r-o-k-e
i'm p-a-i-d
heard about me
i'm sayin'
you got that
you got that milk money
i got that
i got that milf money
you got that
you got that milk money
i got that
i got that milf
i've been
whippin' this up
tippin' this cup
i've been waitin' my turn
i've been workin' so hard
got my spirit turnt up
and i can't stop now
i've been runnin' so long
i've been fighting
so strong
i want it i need it
i got it for real
i love it real woman
i'll feed you this meal
hey mama i did it
the top of the hill
been a minute
don't forget it
mutha fucka i'm ill
now let me see
ya milf shake
let me see ya milf shake
i got that milf money