katy perry - migo
'cause i'm all that you want, boy
all that you can have, boy
got me spread like a buffet
bon app, bon appetit, baby
appetite for seduction
fresh out the oven
melt in your mouth kind of lovin'
bon app, bon appetit, baby
looks like you've been starving
you got those hungry eyes
you cold use some sugar
cause ya levels ain't right
i'm a 5-star michelin
a kobe flown in
you want what i'm cooking, boy
let me take you
under candle light
we can wine and dine
a table for two
and it's okay
if you take your time
eat with your hands, fine
i'm on the menu
'cause i'm all that you want, boy
all that you can have, boy
got me spread like a buffet
bon app, bon appetit, baby
appetite for seduction
fresh out the oven
melt in your mouth kind of lovin'
bon app, bon appetit, baby
so you want some more
well, i'm open 24
wanna keep you satisfied
customer's always right
hope you got some room
for the world's best cherry pie
gonna hit that sweet tooth, boy
let me take you
under candle light
we can wine and dine
a table for two
and it's okay
if you take your time
eat with your hands, fine
i'm on the menu
'cause i'm all that you want, boy
all that you can have, boy
got me spread like a buffet
bon app, bon appetit, baby
appetite for seduction
fresh out the oven
melt in your mouth kind of lovin'.
bon app, bon appetit, baby
'cause i'm all that you want, boy
all that you can have, boy
got me spread like a buffet
bon app, bon appetit, baby
appetite for seduction
fresh out the oven
melt in your mouth kind of lovin'.
bon app, bon appetit, baby
sweet potato pie
it'll change you mind
get you runnin' back for seconds
every single night
i'm the one they say can change your life