I used to bite my tongue and hold my breath Scared to rock the boat and make a mess
So I sat quietly, agreed politely
I guess that I forgot I had a choice I let you push me past the breaking point
I stood for nothing, so I fell for everything
You held me down, but I got up Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice, you hear that sound Like thunder, gonna shake your ground
You held me down, but I got up Get ready cause I've had enough
I see it all, I see it now
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter,
dancing through the fire 'Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar Louder, louder than a lion
Cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar Oh oh oh oh oh oh You're gonna hear me roar
Now I'm floating like a butterfly Stinging like a bee I earned my stripes
I went from zero, to my own hero
You held me down, but I got up Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice, your hear that sound Like thunder, gonna shake your ground
You held me down, but I got up Get ready 'cause I've had enough
I see it all, I see it now
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter,
dancing through the fire 'cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar Louder, louder than a lion
'cause I am a champion
and you're gonna hear me roar Oh oh oh oh oh oh You're gonna hear me roar Oh oh oh oh oh oh