I can swear I can joke I feel my mind if
I drink if I smoke I keep up with the
girls and you see me holding up my
middle finger to the world
your heavens and your pearls girls
cuz I'm not just a pretty girl I'm more
than just a picture I'm a daughter and a
sister sometimes it's hard for me to
show that I'm more than just a rumor or
a song on your computer there's more to
me than people know
some days I'm wrong don't make some rich
zombies
the Sun isn't strong Sundays I quit
but I've been through some [ __ ] I can
swear
[Music]
Giller
girl more than just a number
I'm a hitter
sometimes
me to show that I'm more than just a
title or a comment going viral there's
more to me than people something's wrong
don't even bridge
some days of nice
I quit
don't let it show
some [ __ ] I can swear
yes
thank you
[Music]