can i just turn back the clock
forgive my sins
i just wanna roll my sleeves up
and start again
i don't think i messed it up
time and time again
i just wanna roll my sleeves up
and start again
i was
switching up the lane
stepping out the fame i'm in
i was
pullin on the reigns
sick of all the same happenins
i swear i was
lookin for the same disaster
mixed with a bottle of gin
and just because
i come home after
doesn't mean you take me in
you see my world is spinning like there's nothing you know
you see my world is feeling like it just might explode
and yes i know it's hard to take it backwards
for my mind
need to get it right
need to see some light come in
can i just turn back the clock
forgive my sins
i just wanna roll my sleeves up
and start again
i don't think i messed it up
time and time again
i just wanna roll my sleeves up
and start again
feelin like maybe i'm unappreciated
like my presence in your life has been alleviated
i feel like everything i've done before is different now
but i can see clearer than ever from a distance now
everyday i do it i been goin' through it
but you never knew it cuz i never showed you
you gave me the world so i feel i owed you
but i been lookin through the mirror, that's the old you
imma get it right now, don't know how
but i promise that we're gonna make it somehow
i'm all in, it's from the heart again
open up your mind and maybe we can start again
can i just turn back the clock
forgive my sins
i just wanna roll my sleeves up
and start again