the world can be a nasty place
you know it, i know it, ya
we don't have to fall from grace
put down the weapons you fight with
kill em with kindness
kill em with kindness kill em, kill em
kill em with kindness kill em with kindness
kill em with kindness
go head, go head, go head now
we're running out of time
chasing our lies,
every day a small piece of you dies
always somebody,
you're willing to fight to be right
your lies are bullets,
your mouth's a gun
no war in angry was ever won
put out the fire, before igniting
next time you're fighting
kill em with kindness
kill em with kindness kill em, kill
kill em with kindness kill em with
kill em with kindness
go head, go head, go head now
go head, go head now
your lies are bullets,
your mouth's a gun
no war in angry was ever won
put out the fire, before igniting