take it or leave it
baby take it or leave it
but i know you won't leave it
cause i know that you need it
look in the mirror
when i look in the mirror
baby i see it clearer
why you wanna be nearer
i'm not surprised
i sympathize
i can't deny
your appetite
you got a fetish for my love
i push you out and you come right back
don't see a point in blaming you
if i were you i'd do me too
you got a fetish for my love
i push you out and you come right back
don't see a point in blaming you
if i were you i'd do me too
you got a fetish for my love
reaching your limit
say you're reaching your limit
going over your limit
but i know you can't quit it
something about me
got you hooked on my body
take you over and under and twisted up like origami
i'm not surprised
i sympathize
i can't deny
your appetite
you got a fetish for my love
i push you out and you come right back
don't see a point in blaming you
if i were you i'd do me too
you got a fetish for my love
i push you out and you come right back
don't see a point in blaming you
if i were you i'd do me too
you got a fetish for my love
gucci mane : the way you walk the way you talk
i blame you cause its all your fault
you play hard don't turn me off
you acting hard but i know you soft