this ain't for the best
my reputation's never been worse so
you must like me for me
we can't make any promises
now can we babe
but you can make me a drink
dive bar on the east side
where you at?
phone lights up my nightstand
in the black
come here, you can meet me
in the back
dark jeans and your nikes
look at you
oh damn, never seen that color blue
just think of the fun things we could do...
'cause i like you...
this ain't for the best
my reputation's never been worse so
you must like me for me
yeah i want you...
we can't make any promises
now can we babe
but you can make me a drink
is it cool that i said all that?
is it chill that you're in my head?
'cause i know that it's delicate
is it cool that i said all that?
is it too soon to do this yet?
'cause i know that it's delicate
isn't it, isn't it, isn't it?
isn't it?
isn't it...
delicate
third floor on the west side
me and you
handsome, you're a mansion with a view
do the girls back home touch you
like i do?
long night with your hands
up in my hair
echoes of your footsteps on the stairs
stay here, honey
i don't want to share
'cause i like you...
this ain't for the best
my reputation's never been worse so
you must like me for me
yeah i want you...
we can't make any promises
now can we babe
but you can make me a drink
is it cool that i said all that?
is it chill that you're in my head?
'cause i know that it's delicate
is it cool that i said all that?
is it too soon to do this yet?
'cause i know that it's delicate
isn't it, isn't it, isn't it?
isn't it?
isn't it...
delicate
sometimes i wonder
when you sleep
are you ever dreaming of me?
sometimes when i look into your eyes
i pretend you're mine
all the damn time
'cause i like you
is it cool that i said all that?
is it chill that you're in my head?
'cause i know that it's delicate
(yeah i want you...)
is it cool that i said all that?
is it too soon to do this yet?
'cause i know that it's delicate
'cause i like you
is it cool that i said all that?
isn't it...
is it chill that you're in my head?
isn't it, isn't it,
'cause i know that it's delicate
isn't it...
(yeah i want you...)
is it cool that i said all that?
isn't it...
is it too soon to do this yet?
isn't it, isn't it,
'cause i know that it's delicate
isn't it...