i wanna be your end game
i wanna be your first string
i wanna be your a team
i wanna be your end game end game
big reputation big reputation
ooh you and me we got big reputations
ah and you heard about me
ooh i got some big enemies
big reputation big reputation
ooh you and me would be a big conversation
ah and i heard about you
ooh you like the bad ones too
you so dope don't overdose
i'm so stoked i need a toast
we do the most
i'm in the ghost like i'm whipping a boat
i got a reputation girl that don't precede me
i'm one call away whenever you need me
i'm in a g5
come to the a-side
i gotta bad boy persona it's what they like
you love it, i love it too 'cause you're my type
you hold me down and i protect you with my life
i don't wanna touch you
i don't wanna be
just another ex love
you don't wanna see
i don't wanna miss you
like the other girls do
i don't wanna hurt you i just wanna be
drinking on the beach with you all over me
i know what they all say
but i ain't trying to play
i wanna be your end game
i wanna be your first string
i wanna be your a team
i wanna be your end game end game
knew her when i was young
reconnected when we were little bit older
both sprung, i got issues and chips on
both of my shoulders
reputation precedes me
in rumours i'm knee deep
the truth it its easier to ignore it believe me
even when we'd argue we'd not do it for long
and you understand the good and bad end up in a song
for all your beautiful traits,
and the way you do it with ease
for all my flaws, paranoia, and insecurities
i've made mistakes and made some choices
that's hard to deny
but after the storm, something was
born on the 4th of july
our past days were the fun, this end game is the one
with 4 words on the tip of my tongue, i'll never say
i don't wanna touch you
i don't wanna be
just another ex love
you don't wanna see
i don't wanna miss you
like the other girls do
i don't wanna hurt you
i just wanna be
drinking on the beach with you all over me
i know what they all say
but i ain't trying to play
i wanna be your end game
i wanna be your first string
i wanna be your a team
i wanna be your end game end game
big reputation big reputation
ooh you and me we got big reputations
ah and you heard about me
ooh i got some big enemies
big reputation big reputation
ooh you and me would be a big conversation
ah and i heard about you
ooh you like the bad ones too
i hit you like bang
we tried to forget it but we just couldn't
and i bury hatchets but i keep maps
of where i put 'em
reputation precedes me
they told you i'm crazy
i swear i don't love the drama
it loves me
and i can't let you go
your hand prints on my soul
it's like your eyes are liquor
it's like your body is gold
you've been calling my bluff
on all my usual tricks
so here's the truth from my red lips
i wanna be your end game
i wanna be your first string
i wanna be your a team
i wanna be your end game end game
i wanna be your end game
i wanna be your first string
i wanna be your a team
i wanna be your end game end game