you're on the phone with your girlfriend, she's upset
she's going off about something that you said
cause she doesn't get your humor like i do
i'm in the room, it's a typical tuesday night
i'm listening to the kind of music she doesn't like
and she'll never know your story like i do
but she wears short skirts, i wear t-shirts
she's cheer captain and i'm on the bleachers
dreaming about the day when you wake up and find
that what you're looking for has been here the whole time
if you could see that i'm the one who understands you
been here all along, so why can't you see?
you, you belong with me, you belong with me
walking the streets with you and your worn-out jeans
i can't help thinking this is how it ought to be
laughing on a park bench, thinking to myself
hey, isn't this easy?
and you've got a smile that could light up this whole town
i haven't seen it in a while since she brought you down
you say you're fine, i know you better than that
hey, what ya doing with a girl like that?
she wears high heels, i wear sneakers
she's cheer captain and i'm on the bleachers
dreaming about the day when you wake up and find
that what you're looking for has been here the whole time
if you could see that i'm the one who understands you
been here all along, so why can't you see?
you belong with me
standing by and waiting at your back door
all this time how could you not know
baby, you belong with me, you belong with me
oh, i remember you driving to my house in the middle of the night
i'm the one who makes you laugh
when you know you're 'bout to cry
and i know your favorite songs you tell me 'bout your dreams
think i know where you belong, think i know it's with me
can't you see that i'm the one who understands you
been here all along, so why can't you see?
you belong with me
standing by and waiting at your back door
all this time how could you not know
baby, you belong with me, you belong with me
you belong with me
have you ever thought just maybe