[clock ticking]
[SFX: tires squealing, gun shots, glass breaking]
not tryna be indie
not tryna be cool
just tryna be in this
tell me are you too?
can you feel where the wind is?
can you feel it through
all of the windows
inside this room?
cause i wanna touch you baby
and i wanna feel you too
i wanna see the sun rise
on your sins just me and you
light it up
on the run
let's make love tonight
make it up
fall in love
try
baby i'm right here
but you'll never be alone
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here
i'll hold you when things go wrong
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here~
baby i'm right here
Your life in the daytime is over.
There's eyes on you everywhere.
You know that right?
I'm watching you.
My crews watching you.
You know your little homies?
They pissed off.
They mad at you bro.
Your name is mud on the streets.
Oh, I know who you are.
You don't know me.
we were shut like a jacket
so do your zip
we would roll down the rapids
to find a wave that fits
can you feel where the wind is?
can you feel it through?
all of the windows
inside this room
cause i wanna touch you baby
i wanna feel you too
i wanna see the sun rise
on your sins just me and you
light it up
on the run
let's make love tonight
make it up
fall in love
try
but you'll never be alone
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here
i'll hold you when things go wrong
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here~
baby i'm right here
girl give love to your body
it's only you that can stop it
girl give love to your body~
but you'll never be alone
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here
i'll hold you when things go wrong
i'll be with you from dusk till dawn
baby i'm right here~
baby i'm right here
[Zayn harmonizing]
[car engine revs]